<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aloosefish</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aloosefish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>/books/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/books/reading/</guid>
      <description>+++draft = truedate = 2018-07-30T11:51:47-07:00title = &amp;quot;&amp;quot;slug = &amp;quot;&amp;quot;+++</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas</title>
      <link>/projects/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/ideas/</guid>
      <description>Here are some personal projects I am interested in working on, in no particular order:The Weirdest ThingsAnalyze content tags for front-page news stories of major national newspapers to find the most unusual storiesSee how or if the subject matter has changed over a period of several yearsSans SwaggerUse a neural network to create a rap lyric generatorApplications of agent-based modeling in financial portfolio analysisSegregation studyUse US Census data to rate tracts according to levels of ethnic and racial diversityAs well as incomes, noting in Portland MSA the possible impact of professional athletes’ salaries on mean incomes of blacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best and Worst Neighborhoods in Portland</title>
      <link>/projects/best_and_worst_pdx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/best_and_worst_pdx/</guid>
      <description>This analysis was done for an assignment in the GEOG488 GIS1 course at Portland State University.The geospatial data used in this project is both very large (about 1.6 GB) and not freely distributable. Therefore the resulting report it is presented as a pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Salesforce Administrator and Developer in Portland, Oregon. I like automating things so businesses can spend more time focusing on what really matters.
I am also interested in basketball, cycling, literature, and space travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Ian Davisian@aloosefish.comSkillsCertified Salesforce AdministratorAdept user of declarative and non-declarative (Python, Apex, SQL) reporting and automation toolsExperience supporting data-intensive applications for a global customer baseEducationTrailhead.Salesforce.com/me/ianthedavis
2019
Learned Salesforce Administration and Development by earning over 100 course completion badges.
DataCamp.com/profile/aloosefish
2018
Learned how to analyze data and create reports using Python and R by completing 29 interactive courses. Integrated these skills into college coursework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WR327_Example</title>
      <link>/projects/wr327_example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/wr327_example/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>